hey guys let's get ready for a stunning
festive look today start off by using an
eyebrow definer to line shape and fill
your brows prep your eyelids with a
concealer start your eye makeup with the
neutral shade add some shimmer and
intensify with an eyeliner don't forget
to curl your lashes with loads of
mascara
start your face makeup with a primer
this will give you a smooth base for
your makeup add some face mask before
applying foundation always go for a
foundation that matches your skin tone
and your undertone next up is concealer
fix the dark circles and the
pigmentation with it after that use a
powder to avoid your makeup from
creasing next up is bronzer blush and
highlighter play around with some
colored gold and black holes opt for
bold red lip shade next and wrap up the
look by setting your makeup with a
setting list
and tada you're done